module.exports = [
  {
    question: "How many guitars does Taylor Swift have?",
    answers: ["13", "22", "She lost count in 2007"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "First Song Taylor Swift learned on the guitar?",
    answers: [
      "Kiss me by sixpence none the richer",
      "Our Song by Taylor Swift",
      "Blank Space by Taylor Swift",
    ],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Taylor Swift's favorite subject in school?",
    answers: ["Math", "English", "Science"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Taylor Swift's favorite cocktail?",
    answers: ["Vodka and diet coke", "Pina colada", "Negroni"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is one thing Taylor Swift should always have in the fridge?",
    answers: ["Gluten free cookies", "Humus", "Nuts"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "When was Taylor Swift's debut album released?",
    answers: ["October 24, 2006", "October 26, 2006", "October 24, 2007"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following are not released yet? (Last updated April 13, 2023)",
    answers: [
      "Red (Taylor's Version)",
      "Fearless (Taylor's Version)",
      "Reputation (Taylor's Version)",
    ],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Taylor Swift song is about Jake Gyllenhaal?",
    answers: [
      "All To Well (10 Minute Version) (Taylor's Version) (From the Vault)",
      "Style",
      "Lavender Haze",
    ],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which song is not from Reputation?",
    answers: [
      "So it goes",
      "â€¦Ready For It?",
      "The last great American dynasty",
    ],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What Song is the opening act on The Era's Tour?",
    answers: [
      "Lavender Haze",
      "Miss Americana and the heartbreak prince",
      "Cardigan",
    ],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who stole Taylor Swift's songs?",
    answers: ["Jake Gyllenhaal", "John Mayer", "Scooter Brown"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Best Singer in the world?",
    answers: [
      "Taylor Swift (choose this option)",
      "Taylor Swift",
      "Taylor Swift",
    ],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Who Co-produced the album Midnights with Taylor Swift?",
    answers: ["Max Martin", "Jack Antonoff", "Ryan Tedder"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What Song is the closing act on The Reputation Stadium Tour?",
    answers: [
      "Dress",
      "Call It What You Want",
      "This Is Why We Can't Have Nice Things",
    ],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is Taylor Swift's Boyfriend? (I don't care about the rumors!!)",
    answers: ["Joe Alwyn", "Harry Styles", "John Mayer"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is Taylor Swift's Best Friend?",
    answers: ["Selena Gomez", "Justin Bieber", "Hailey Bieber"],
    correct: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which song is about Taylor Swift's mom?",
    answers: [
      "ME! (feat. Brendon Urie of Panic! At The Disco) ft. Brendon Urie (Lover)",
      "Soon You'll Get Better (Lover)",
      "All Too Well (Taylor's Version)",
    ],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who took the microphone from Taylor Swift on stage after winning the VMA awards in 2009?",
    answers: ["Scooter Brown", "John Mayer", "Kanye West"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which album is Taylor Swift's comeback after the Kanye West and Kim Kardashian drama?",
    answers: ["Lover", "Evermore", "Reputation"],
    correct: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which Album was released at the beginning of the pandemic in 2020?",
    answers: ["Midnights", "Folklore", "Evermore"],
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What Song is the closing act on The Era's Tour?",
    answers: ["Lavender Haze", "Karma", "Illicit Affairs"],
    correct: 1,
  },
];
